NANCY QUINN

8745 Telegraph Way ~ Seattle, Washington 98136

SUMMARY OF QUALIFICATIONS

MBA Applicant ~ Technology Commercialization Focus

Accomplished, dynamic professional and PhD with more than five years of experience conducting high-level scientific research. Motivated by challenge to improve business model for science-driven ventures. Proactive leader and team player integral to success of numerous research initiatives. Dedicated scholar with strong teaching experience and strategic approach to problem solving. Diplomatic supervisor with sophisticated knowledge of multicultural and interdisciplinary teams. Resourceful and versatile with excellent interpersonal skills, highly developed work ethic, and reputation for integrity. Fluent in English and Chinese.

EDUCATION

STATE UNIVERSITY, Seattle, Washington Doctor of Philosophy in Medicinal Chemistry, 2006

UNIVERSITY OF THE NORTHWEST, Seattle, Washington *Bachelor of Science in Chemistry*, 2001

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

NORTHWEST COLLEGE OF MEDICINE, Seattle, Washington

2010

Postdoctoral Researcher

206-555-1212

• Designed and conducted research to extend study potential for duration of an organism's lifetime.

INSTITUTE OF CHEMICAL BIOLOGY, Seattle, Washington

2006 - 2009

nancyq@net.com

Visiting Scientist

• Expressed and purified mutant proteins then analyzed impact of site-directed mutants.

2002 - 2006

- DEPARTMENT OF CHEMISTRY, STATE UNIVERSITY, Seattle, Washington Research Assistant
- Discovered and developed anti-tuberculosis agents that can overcome multi-drug resistant TB.
- Designed and synthesized second generation anticancer agents and drug resistance reversal agents.
- Obtained collaborators, trained team, supervised junior members, and maintained instruments.

TEACHING EXPERIENCE

SCIENCE COMPETITION, Seattle, Washington

2003 & 2004

Mentor to High School Seniors

• Motivated students to develop curiosity about science, helping two contestants reach semi-finals.

DEPARTMENT OF CHEMISTRY, Seattle, Washington

2001 - 2002

Graduate Teaching Assistant

- Lectured class of 40 undergraduates, monitored students in labs, and evaluated performances.
- Facilitated learning and improved performance by tutoring students individually and in small groups.



NANCY QUINN PAGE TWO

TEACHING EXPERIENCE

(Continued)

STATE COLLEGE, Seattle, Washington *Private Tutor, Math and English*

1998 - 2000

AWARDS

- *Chemistry Award* for Excellence in Doctoral Research (2007).
- Washington State Travel Award, Travel Co. Inc., Seattle, (Fall 2003, Fall 2004, Spring 2005).

PROFESSIONAL AFFILIATION

AMERICAN CHEMICAL SOCIETY *Member*

2003 - Present

SCIENTIFIC COLLABORATIONS

- International Medical Center, Research Institute, Department of Infectious Diseases
- State University, Department of Microbiology, Immunology, and Pathology
- University of the Northwest, Department of Pharmacological Sciences
- Washington State Cancer Institute

